=Revenge of Royal Princess=
= انتقام الأميرة الملكية =
=Episode 20=
= الحلقة 20 =
I heard that there has been a estrangement
سمعت أن هناك قطيعة
between His Royal Highness and you recently.
بينك وبين صاحب السمو الملكي مؤخرًا.
It appears to be true.
يبدو أنه صحيح.
Sister.
أخت.
You don't even have a maid by your side now.
ليس لديك حتى خادمة بجانبك الآن.
In my opinion,
فى رايى،
His Royal Highness will not protect you anymore.
لن يحميك صاحب السمو الملكي بعد الآن.
Do you think I need protection?
هل تعتقد أنني بحاجة للحماية؟
Shu.
شو.
Sister.
أخت.
Get out.
اخرج.
Your Royal Highness.
صاحب السمو الملكي.
It hurts.
هذا مؤلم.
What happened to you?
ماذا حدث لك؟
You poisoned me?
هل سممتني؟
Let me help you.
دعني اساعدك.
Han Shu.
هان شو.
Sister.
أخت.
I feel so hot.
انا اشعر بألحر كثير.
Sober now?
رصين الآن؟
Leave.
يترك.
Leave now!
ارحل الآن!
Han Shu.
هان شو.
Are you thinking of Miss Xie?
هل تفكر في الآنسة شيه؟
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Look.
ينظر.
Xie Yugui is now Princess Yong'an,
Xie Yugui هي الآن الأميرة Yong'an ،
my sister.
أختى.
If you marry her,
إذا تزوجتها ،
you have to call me brother.
عليك الاتصال بي يا أخي.
Come on.
تعال.
Brother.
أخ.
Your Majesty, you are really treacherous.
جلالة الملك ، أنت غادر حقًا.
Not as treacherous as you.
ليس غدرا مثلك.
You knew that you could bear the medicine,
كنت تعلم أنه يمكنك تحمل الدواء ،
but you still pretended to be pitiful,
لكنك ما زلت تتظاهر بالشفقة ،
making Miss Xie feel sorry for you.
جعل الآنسة شيه تشعر بالأسف من أجلك.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Not like you.
ليس مثلك.
Nobody would feel sorry for you.
لا أحد سيشعر بالأسف من أجلك.
Han Shu, you went so far.
هان شو ، لقد ذهبت بعيدا.
Yao.
ياو.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Xie Yugui ruined my plan.
دمر Xie Yugui خطتي.
Dad.
أب.
Do me a favor.
أعمل لي معروفا.
Let's
دعونا
get rid of her forever.
تخلص منها إلى الأبد.
(The right of communication through network)
(حق الاتصال عبر الشبكة)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent.)
(تنتمي حصريًا إلى Tencent.)